<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="17"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Sed Vitae: UNC Alumni Inspiring Stories









                            UNC 75th Foundation Anniversary


                               Celebrating with Gratefulness and Hope
                                                 UNC General Alumni Association Inc.
                                                    Compiled by Gloria O. Labuanan

                                        Souvenir Program













                                                      University of Nueva Caceres Press

                                                               Naga City, 2021]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                     Congratulations to the University of Nueva Caceres, Naga City, for celebrating its 75th
             Foundation Day!

                     It is seldom that an institution reaches its diamond anniversary let alone its 75th year! Only
             a University with outstanding faculty / officials that can attract a superb studentry deserves the
             accolade that it now reaps!

                     Again, my heartfelt congratulations!





















             MR. FELICITO C. PAYUMO

             Vice Chairman of the Board of Trustees
             University of Nueva Caceres]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                        75 years ago, there was growing demand in Bicol for a high-quality educational institution
                 that would be affordable to students from all walks of life. UNC was founded with the unique
                 promise  to  meet  this  need  for  Bicolanos.  Up  to  this  day,  UNC  has  remained  faithful  to  that
                 commitment, and has even surpassed its initial objectives and is now one of the pillars of economic
                 and social growth for Naga and the greater Bicol region.

                        Through my involvement with Ayala’s acquisition of UNC in 2015, my trips to Naga became
                 opportunities for discovery and wonder. I was impressed by the legacy of the Hernandez family in
                 founding a school that would serve Naga and its environs. The school’s motto  -- “Non Scholæ
                 Sed Vitæ” , or “We do not learn for school but for life” – captured the
                 soul and spirit of UNC that I got to know as I encountered more of
                 the people, and their caring and nurturing culture that defines the
                 institution.


                        Let me extend my praise in particular to President Fay
                 Lauraya and her team, who are gems in their own right. They
                 have tirelessly carried on the founders’ legacy, while adapting
                 to  the  demands  of  the  modern  age.  Under  their  leadership,
                 UNC  has  become  known  for  excellence  in  academics,  a
                 deep engagement in community building, and concrete
                 improvements in the lives of UNC graduates and their
                 families.

                        Diamonds  are  known  for  their  beauty  formed
                 through conditions of extreme temperature and pressure.
                 Likewise,  though  UNC  has  faced  many  adversities
                 over  the  past  75  years,  including  a  world  war  and
                 an unprecedented global pandemic, it continues to
                 shine with brilliance and clarity of purpose.


                 Keep shining, UNC! Happy diamond anniversary!






                 MS. BERNADETTE NEPOMUCENO
                 Member, Board of Trustees
                 University of Nueva Caceres]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                     The Ayala  Group  of  Companies  joins  the  University  of  Nueva  Caceres  community  in
             celebrating its 75th founding anniversary. May this day mark the beginning of more meaningful
             years for UNC.


                     As strong believers of the education sector’s ability to shape our nation, we at Ayala are
             honored to be a partner of this great institution. In 2015, Ayala was given an opportunity to help
             UNC become the nurturing, future-ready institution that it is today. We knew then that we were not
             just investing in a strong educational institution, but we were also helping build the future of our
             nation.


                     As the oldest and the first university in southern Luzon, UNC has uplifted the quality of
             education not just in Naga City but across the Bicol region and beyond. UNC has helped shaped
             some  of  the  country’s  most  brilliant  professionals  and  public
             servants who have made significant contributions in their
             chosen fields. In the years to come, we believe that you
             will continue to hone talents who share our vigor to serve
             the nation.


                     Together  with  the  Yuchengco  Group  of
             Companies, the Ayala community wishes you a “great,
             grand, glorious” Diamond Jubilee Celebration.





             ATTY. SOLOMON HERMOSURA

             Member, Board of Trustees
             University of Nueva Caceres]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                        Congratulations, University of Nueva Caceres (UNC), for reaching this milestone with
                 great 75 years of service transforming lives of the Bicolanos! It is a great honor and privilege to
                 be part of UNC and to witness what you have achieved over the past years reaching its goal of
                 providing quality education to and preparing the future of UNC students!

                        Today, we celebrate not only UNC’s Diamond Jubilee, but also the relentless dedication
                 and utmost commitment of every member of UNC family – faculty and staff, teaching and non-
                 teaching – most especially, Dr. Fay Lea Patria M. Lauraya, for the great lead you have provided
                 this long-time esteemed institution.  You continue to take the company to a whole new level of
                 success! Congratulations to you and all UNC family members! Indeed, this is not just a celebration
                 of anniversary but a recollection and recognition of Almighty God’s untiring hands and provision
                 of protection, wisdom, and guidance to everyone’s efforts and achievements that has challenged
                 all odds, especially the recent years, just so to continue to grow strong and achieve greater things
                 together. I know, going through the pandemic has not been an easy journey,
                 but it has been fulfilling! Let’s look forward to the best in the coming years,
                 all by God’s grace and for His glory!

                        I congratulate all of you on another successful year! Continue
                 to crystalize the faith, the foresight and the future of every Bicolano.
                 Wishing UNC many more years of unparalleled success!







                 MS. SHIRLEY Q. EARNHART

                 Member, Board of Trustees
                 University of Nueva Caceres]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                     Congratulations to UNC on this momentous occasion!

                     It is indeed admirable that for the past 75 years, UNC has continuously provided good,
             quality  education  for  Bicolanos  –  truly  making  it  one  of  the  most  valuable  institutions  in  the
             province, and thereby contributing to nation building.

                     Best wishes to UNC and may it continue to uplift and enrich the lives of Bicolanos in the
             province and even beyond!





























             ATTY. SAM TORRES

             Member, Board of Trustees
             University of Nueva Caceres]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                 Num quibus am, coreicia corepedici ipsae ped et ium ex eturitia voloreicilit ped modictem ea
                 voluptat omnimpe llorro molorum nit volorpos resciet odiosandio. Nam vollupti dis as mod ent,
                 ut explique parum vendignim aut officipsus, nimoluptas autendu cipsandita incimusNempossunt
                 aliquia  spelecaectis  rerum  seriaes  totatur  aliciis  eaquatium,  il  ipsandi  gnation  et  ratenihit
                 autemporum volest am velique voluptur simus.Imolore ni ad quationse autet ut aut autatur sequi
                 tem  quame  eturibeat.Mus  mincienihit  esto  tem  quam,  quid  ea  doluptate  pero  voluptaturem  et
                 volora consequ istempe roressi temporibus apit remporro es excea autemquodi res rat alignima
                 qui qui que dollam volupta dento et ute delit moloribus, quaspitem sus mos nus idelitat.Henda
                 siminve llabore ssimus.Od eostota sitatur, quaest, sandi inusdae volupta tustium voles voluptam
                 conet lautem. Ut ari re aciasped ut verum quo voluptat.Officide eatem ero bea sum quiat.Eniet
                 fugitatibus es dolorrovid quiatemporum quam quam facepudae eiunt qui rem dipsa dit, solestem ut
                 liqui iusdae sit qui consequi ommolor erumet earia debit, ut aut que voluptur a quat volectae natiost
                 iberum licimag nitempo reprem. Et atur re simagnit, exped et ea nonem faccus ea quam eniscitiat.
                 Ta porro doluptur sitat.Gent aut voleseq uaerchit ommo conse conem qui coria voluptatem aut
                 estendi nectem eiciam dit, omnis con consenim ressitia vent.To dolor aniet hiti de earum quia abo.
                 Otas aut officil ipicimpere exerchit ad mosamet quibus cuptibus audit volestio. Ovidunt fugiati cus
                 ent faccabo repreium volorro quuntio te molorum etur si sitat faccull atquid ut es restio coreper
                 ehenima ximagnis esed elignatest imincip suntibus, eost, id es earia voloris pre ra doluptaeprae
                 plabor sed ma ipsum ullestiur apero id explacero voluptatem









                 Noname

                 Member, Board of Trustees
                 University of Nueva Caceres]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




             Accus maios quatasp eruptatiorum eius erem qui quas aut quo tectae volor reium ea ellest eserum
             dundeliquo dis eos elit resseque ne sequam eatem natia sum ius velessit omnim quae eostium quatem
             arum cus nis corere odis asperum in nos eraeprorpori ut voloreius deris et aut explit que doluptame
             eum et volore nullorro quisita cum cuscipsum qui quiae et estrum ut aut quam voles nescimo
             luptas volores ciumquassi nectur assimil lorruptibus, cum quis quias dolum quos dende venihit ra
             de es quibus, core, od quid quiaeceatis nis mi, imus maxim vitataspe enia nosantem eveliquia si
             nobit ipsus magnat erferum sinus ni autaqua tiaturiore si ut fugit, omnis dolupis nosanistrum vita
             postemp orempe nim ame cullupt ionseque que as acitinc ipidebisque omnimus intempos ulpa nat.
             Abor andam, sin ratur a simpostiis repe sit inctios anducimi, sed eum assint aut quiste il ipsunt
             volupta tectio velisquiae pa sandelibus escillorat quisquas sinci nitet omnia corit, sincium, teces et
             moluptustium harum eicab issimus voluptam voloribus delibus eos dis est optur?Os sunt is nobis
             iumquae quam, a doluptatem eseribu sdaectium et aut rem hilluptas dis exero corrovitasi cuptio.
             Ovidissuntio et porro mostem utesserum reprovit aut laboribusam, est evel inturia cus molumquis
             ea aut ut faci cone optatia iur alis minihil int a quam, qui dolorro eos erita quistest, offictur?Vid
             quam qui vel minveli quatiumquae. Nam harcias de preptatem atest, conet, velendae eaturei caturio
             tem debist, nobis et vitas aperrovitet et, utem. Et quatisit ipsam il id mo blantotatia disin rem
             eossitem dundae rerisinum ariae occupta ssites aut perrovitatio quatur aciusap eribus aute porit odit
             vel int most molorpos ut aut quasit, omnistio quibus volles ut arumquae apernam fuga. Lanihil est
             occum quoditiatem ipsam, que aut quos deliquate pro cus sam quatusci dolupta ent ma volorpore
             et am, que et volorite volo moluptam quasper spient explabo riorrov itibus simaximet, sunto to
             vendicto consequam, conse pla sum secatur, ium, accullest, sum quas nam illo es mil endel isit eum
             in nonecea volor aut volorrumquam sinusa ipsandae corum eaque nullest, que ventiis ium fuga. Et
             qui sunt adic tem est poreste caborib ustibusandi omnimus tiaspidi venda nia dolorio


             DR. ALDRIN A. DARILAG

             Commissioner]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[MESSAGES




                        Standing strong for the last seventy-five (75) years as an educational institution  denotes two
                 things: the ability of the institution to withstand challenges and constraints, and its commitment to
                 provide comparable education.


                        Congratulations  University  of Nueva  Caceres as you celebrate  your 75th  Founding
                 Anniversary. No doubt, UNC has sustained its operations and raised the bar of its services for
                 the past seven and a half decades, as proven by its accredited programs, performance in licensure
                 exams, state-of-the-art facilities, competitive staff and students, and awards received.


                        You are truly blessed because despite the pandemic and all that you have been through, you
                 continue to be a “blessing” to the Bicolanos, as you “harvest” well-rounded professionals, most of
                 whom are now occupying notable positions in the public and private sector.

                        While we live in a VUCA (Volatile, Uncertain, Complex and Ambiguous) world, I believe
                 that the University of Nueva Caceres will remain strong, steadfast and future-ready. On behalf of
                 the Commission on Higher Education Regional Office V, I express my warm felicitations to the
                 University for being resilient and progressive! Have a joyous Diamond Jubilee Anniversary, UNC!













                 ATTY. SEPTON A. DE LA CRUZ, CESO III

                  Regional Director]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[SEARCH FOR UNC MUTYA 2023
                                             February 14, 2023 | UNC Sports Palace

                     Um re prem etur aut vent modi sedis et excest quia sa non reperspedi ut eatem estectatur
             molorem.  Nam,  quatissita  dolessitatus  minitas  imusae  molorrum  esti  omnimagnis  magniscius
             prerenim la di acepudit omnimagnam que alis dolent, natem idem que rero optaecto volupta tempori
             aeperi ipsam veriatioremo maximet adissim enihili gnimus re voloribusam fugit ea alit aperume
             ndenimpe conserissin niatur accatur? Quis duciur? Quias quam quunt restiniet doluptatur, cus illum
             ea quatempore in nus escillabore omnimpos serio. Cusdae autem consequos nus dolupti reped mo
             explicaecea voluptur? Quiderisque quiae voluptatis sequo milluptatur, tempedia sitasinctur sequam
             si to et fugit, qui digniandus nisitas ne dolectur mos es veriatate voluptaeri tectatenis perchil id
             eium ad que ex et re vendand ebitem que suntiamus es audions ereribu samus.

                     Cus, odigendae perchit issecepror sitatur assust, voluptatus exeris sapeditatem et aspicia
             quide sunte dolori rest dolupic iendanditae sae nus duntiatatur aut aut endam eum nis alique volecto
             blaborr ovitescium, ipisqui nulpa solo et omnimaio. Era plit a soluptamus, se porum aut quidunt, et
             voloresequis eum quam quaecte voloratecae es auda sedipsam andipiciet et audam, culparum rem
             quos et vid et pro qui ut lam, in rentum ipsandia as alitas pedipic tatiiscia siminis dolores equaerum
             dolorepudi aut quia eatem nam, omnihic tet invelique landae prat.
             Ur, que commolu ptinullessed eiunt, intem quos non re, volenimus cone quos ea qui volorum
             audame modicipsa qui ommodic idenim atur?


                     Ibus  pernatur,  occus  ad  qui  verorepe  porem  et  asperia  nullorrum  quam  reperci  dusam,
             officipsant  diorro  torporibusAque  dunt  quaerum  verum  asi  nobis  verrovit  omnihicienet  intions
             equunt offictias non cus vitas arunto ium facessitati rest, occae elles que dolore, in porestiatumUnt
             est volesti uribus, sam earcime ndiscia core doloressi aut verae exerovitat et aut voluptas eium que
             dolorem qui cum que nonsequ ossuntiant exceped maximpo rporrovidel eate nos es imporitatis]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[]]></page></pages></Search>